{
    "subject": "resource/Soviet_Union",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Soviet Union",
    "human_readable": "The label of Soviet Union is Soviet Union.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9655535817146301,
            "question": "What is the label of Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017207622528076,
            "question": "Is the label of Soviet Union accurate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6418376564979553,
            "question": "What are some key events associated with the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5934677124023438,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569056868553162,
            "question": "Who were some prominent leaders of the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.521746039390564,
            "question": "What was the political system of the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5189328193664551,
            "question": "When did the Soviet Union exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102130770683289,
            "question": "What existed during the time period of the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49678340554237366,
            "question": "What are some cultural aspects associated with the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4340410828590393,
            "question": "How did the Soviet Union impact the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Soviet Union is Soviet Union.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9246_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural aspects associated with the Soviet Union?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9246_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What existed during the time period of the Soviet Union?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9246_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Soviet Union exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9246_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9246_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about the Soviet Union, and one of them states that it was also called \"Soviet Union\" on-file. This suggests that the label of the Soviet Union is indeed \"Soviet Union\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the provided context information which clearly refers to entities and their labels as \"The Soviet Union\" multiple times, thus supporting the triple \"The label of Soviet Union is Soviet Union.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}